<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<FFINC>
<Projects>

<Project>
<Name>MODULAR STEEL BUILDING, HANGZHOU, CHINA /HT</Name>
<Desc>Full structural design and preparing structural package documentation (Structural Layout drawings + Calculation sheet) of steel modular building consisting of 77 modules.
</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture>assets/images/9c3547214e7ae686c21492c252cd71fa_ALL_Structure_3D.jpg</Picture>
<Picture>assets/images/80465902ccf6e857844cbef8d6510b43_Zoom_2.jpg</Picture>
<Picture>assets/images/c723afeebbcda5f0673a61007142f102_Zoom_3.jpg</Picture>

</Pictures>

</Project>






<Project>
<Name>BIM MODELING AND STRUCTURAL DESIGN OF INDUSTRIAL PLANT - GERMANY KZ</Name>
<Desc>Our Client required structural BIM modeling and structural modeling and design of a 10500m2 industrial facility consisting of a steel structure with adjacent concrete administrative buildings.All steel and concrete elements and slabs were successfully modeled in Revit structure 2017 and later exported to a 3D structural model for analysis of base reaction and steel design to Eurocode 3.A full 3D BIM and model of was presented along with a detailed structural analysis and design report containing all the design parameters and results.</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture>assets/images/69c2b1e6528d320e981f171e295e569f_Porsche_B63_Manufacturing_FacilityBIM.jpg</Picture>
<Picture>assets/images/27ae7c09852ea3b2bcc73c7d2c522c8e_Porsche_B63_Manufacturing_Facility.jpg</Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>







<Project>
<Name>RC Analysis and Design of Residential Building - Germany
</Name>

<Desc>
our Client required to create a 3D structural analysis model out of a 6- story residential building a BIM model to: 

    1. Analyze the effect of the lateral loads (wind) on the walls and columns of the structure. 
 2. Obtain the Pile foundation reactions. 
 3. Design the slabs and foundation raft to EN1992-1-1:2004 incorporating Corrigendum dated January 2008.  
  
All the required tasks were done successfully including modifications to the original package. An accurate structural model and a detailed analysis and design report were presented maintaining the client satisfaction.  
</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture>assets/images/338585e7b3ec4c48a967d84fb39f920a_5_Storey_Residential_BuildingBIM.JPG</Picture>
<Picture>assets/images/a137df950e9cd6af77c15bc7b12d6719_5_Storey_Residential_Building.JPG</Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>







<Project>
<Name>Structural Modeling of Composite truss elements - Germany</Name>
<Desc>
  Creating and analysis of Composite truss using SAP2000 and then modeling supports as solid structure. In order to perform structural revision of an existing arched sawtooth roof over a sports hall.
</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture>assets/images/92ca7cc68922068af32e51b357033a59_FEM_Models.JPG</Picture>
<Picture>assets/images/c88de34b645fb87bfeb351c8411b8236_P1060660.JPG</Picture>
<Picture>assets/images/5045c60ddfbb3bcc1d11b9763e294bae_P1060670.JPG</Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>




<Project>
<Name>Structural modeling of 14 floor Building 
New Zealand</Name>
<Desc>
  Full structural modelling of 14 floor steel building with seismic isolators using SAP2000. Applying all loads according to AS/NZS 1170.</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture>assets/images/1257c229a21cb854a7269b6b52479102_Cathedreal_Towers_NZ.PNG</Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>




<Project>
<Name> Structural design of Cooler steel platform to AISC 360-10  
</Name>
<Desc>
Preparing Finite element model and structural report for a steel platform carrying fluid coolers. All the checks of different elements were carried out to AISC 360-10 in addition to checking resonance due to dynamic vibrations of the fans.  

</Desc><Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture>assets/images/b3aebbb768f70ef1ce932448e7fadfd4_Actual_FEM.JPG</Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>





<Project>
<Name>   Multi-Storey Factory Extension - Germany  
 
</Name>
<Desc>
  3D modeling and analysis of the factory extension building using ETABS and generating of a full structural analysis report. 
</Desc>
 <Profile></Profile>
<Pictures>
<Picture>assets/images/7dbb5d3cfa15b72cf40cc41a61d80418_4_Storey_Factory_Extension_Ostfildern.jpg</Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>




<Project>
<Name>     Steel production hall- Germany     

 
</Name>
<Desc>
<i>Total area: 8000m2 Total structural steel weight: 600 tons.</i>
  Full Structural design and preparing structural package documentation ( Structural Layout Drawings + Calculation sheet) of a steel production hall with crane girders to EC3. 
</Desc>
  <Pictures>
<Picture>assets/images/011a924435c9f1240b653731a63d178f_8000m2_590T_Industrial_Hall_Ebermannsdorf.JPG</Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>




</Projects>

<Services>
</Services>

<Team></Team>

</FFINC>

