<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<FFINC>
<Projects>

<Project>
<Name>MODULAR STEEL BUILDING, HANGZHOU, CHINA /HT</Name>
<Desc>Full structural design and preparing structural package documentation (Structural Layout drawings + Calculation sheet) of steel modular building consisting of 77 modules.
</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture></Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>






<Project>
<Name>BIM MODELING AND STRUCTURAL DESIGN OF INDUSTRIAL PLANT - GERMANY KZ</Name>
<Desc>Our Client required structural BIM modeling and structural modeling and design of a 10500m2 industrial facility consisting of a steel structure with adjacent concrete administrative buildings.All steel and concrete elements and slabs were successfully modeled in Revit structure 2017 and later exported to a 3D structural model for analysis of base reaction and steel design to Eurocode 3.A full 3D BIM and model of was presented along with a detailed structural analysis and design report containing all the design parameters and results.</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture></Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>







<Project>
<Name>RC Analysis and Design of Residential Building - Germany
</Name>

<Desc>
our Client required to create a 3D structural analysis model out of a 6- story residential building a BIM model to: 

    1. Analyze the effect of the lateral loads (wind) on the walls and columns of the structure. 
 2. Obtain the Pile foundation reactions. 
 3. Design the slabs and foundation raft to EN1992-1-1:2004 incorporating Corrigendum dated January 2008.  
  
All the required tasks were done successfully including modifications to the original package. An accurate structural model and a detailed analysis and design report were presented maintaining the client satisfaction.  
</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture></Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>







<Project>
<Name>Structural Modeling of Composite truss elements - Germany</Name>
<Desc>
  Creating and analysis of Composite truss using SAP2000 and then modeling supports as solid structure. In order to perform structural revision of an existing arched sawtooth roof over a sports hall.
</Desc>
<Profile></Profile>

<Pictures>
<Picture></Picture>
</Pictures>

</Project>




</Projects>

<Services>
</Services>

<Team></Team>

</FFINC>

